{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089221809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089221808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089231576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089231575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089245428","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089245428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 8929a6e6-87c8-4f58-9af8-62405e7d7148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089250623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089250623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 8929a6e6-87c8-4f58-9af8-62405e7d7148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089280474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089280473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 8929a6e6-87c8-4f58-9af8-62405e7d7148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089290349","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089290349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 8929a6e6-87c8-4f58-9af8-62405e7d7148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089297940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089297940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 8929a6e6-87c8-4f58-9af8-62405e7d7148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089303919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089303918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 8929a6e6-87c8-4f58-9af8-62405e7d7148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089308008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089308008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 8929a6e6-87c8-4f58-9af8-62405e7d7148"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089355491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089355491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfu_mlu_ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089362177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089362176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mwu_mu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089368919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089368919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mpe_bi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089376979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089376979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_ko_la"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089385404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089385404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mvu_ndi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089393198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089393198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_cha_mko"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089400410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089400410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_swa_si_ni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089407771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089407771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_nja_we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089416542","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089416542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mtu_mbi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089426580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089426580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mtu_mbi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089438224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089438222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_093327"," gameId":" 359486f1-1226-4f65-8a7e-3ff9b44349a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ni_mtu_mbi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}